President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Website of the Office of the President, 2013 May 2 - 2017 July 17; 16; 83 captures
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 July 17
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host rna.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host slsc.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host uaems.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host uapps.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host wiki.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_DELAY for host library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: BLOCK_URL meg.library.albany.edu:8080/archive/search?(STRING_MATCH) for host meg.library.albany.edu (created 2017-05-11, last updated 2017-05-11)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL http://www.atmos.albany.edu/facstaff/wkidd(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL http://www.atmos.albany.edu/geology/theses/(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL www.ctg.albany.edu/(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    start_date: 2017-07-17T16:55:09Z
    original_start_date: 2017-07-17T16:55:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-07-23T00:21:36Z
    end_date: 2017-07-22T17:19:10Z
    elapsed_ms: 433389662
    discovered_count: 2896967
    novel_count: 383574
    duplicate_count: 1260379
    queued_count: 1253014
    downloaded_count: 1643953
    download_failures: 389
    warc_revisit_count: 1260323
    warc_url_count: 1643823
    total_data_in_kbs: 242227760
    duplicate_bytes: 230083618880
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3691503039
    doc_rate: 3.79
    kb_rate: 558.0